{"questions":[{"question":"what is the differance between black box and white box testing?","answer":["in black box testing, the software is unknown, but in white box testing, the software structure is known","in black box testing all tests performed to uncover erroneous outputs, but in white box the does not","in black box testing you can create a flow graph but in white box testing you can't","black box testing is more effective than white box testing"],"correct_ans":"in black box testing, the software is unknown, but in white box testing, the software structure is known","level":"EASY","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"select the factors that effect the required intensity of quality assurance activities:","answer":["percentage of old members in the team","technical complexity","magnitude of the project","2 +3 are correct"],"correct_ans":"4","level":"EASY","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"who can be in both walkthrough and inspection activities?","answer":["coder","maintenance oracle","producer","standards bearer"],"correct_ans":"3","level":"EASY","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"what is correct abput requirments errors types:","answer":["missing requirements are easy to identify","partial requirements and conflicting requirements are the same","excess requirements is a requirement that has been described in the dociment, but it is not part of the project","none of them"],"correct_ans":"3","level":"EASY","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"which sentence is correct?","answer":["agile process is the right software process to work with","plan driven process is the right software process to work with","if practical process include elements of agile process it cannot include elements of plan driven process","there is no right or wrong software process "],"correct_ans":"4","level":"EASY","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"select the wrong sentence of sprint review meeting","answer":["team presents what it accomplished during the sprint","starts with: Product demo led by product owner","ends with: sprint retrospective led by product owner","informal 2 - hour prep time rule"],"correct_ans":"3","level":"EASY","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"select the correct example of connectors:","answer":["streaming connectors","shared memory connectors","distribution connectors","all the above"],"correct_ans":"4","level":"HARD","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"which of these models is usually described using UML models?","answer":["a computation independent model (CIM)","a platform independent model (PIM)","platform specific models (PSM)","none of them"],"correct_ans":"2","level":"HARD","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"what is the product owner?","answer":["the owner of the project","the person who represents the customer interest","a developer from the team of developers","none of them"],"correct_ans":"2","level":"HARD","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"alpha and beta testing are types of:","answer":["unit testing","program testing","user testing","software testing"],"correct_ans":"user testing","level":"MEDIUM","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"Lehman's laws can be applicable to:","answer":["shrink-wrapped software products","small organizations","medium sized systems","large, toilored systems developed by large orgnizations"],"correct_ans":"large, toilored systems developed by large orgnizations","level":"MEDIUM","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"software evolution processes does not depend on:","answer":["the skills and experience of the people involved","the amount of people involved","the type of software being maintained","the development processes used"],"correct_ans":"the amount of people involved","level":"MEDIUM","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"the rist managment process does not include:","answer":["risk monitoring","risk analysis","risk planning","risk evalutaion"],"correct_ans":"4","level":"MEDIUM","team":"Chimp"},{"question":"which sentence is false about user stories?","answer":["we get them by setting down with our customers asking a lots of questions","they are written on index cards to encourage face to face communication","user story and use case are the same thing","they are features our customers might one day like to see in thier software"],"correct_ans":"3","level":"MEDIUM","team":"Chimp"}]}